**Full Stack Developer** 

+213775225061

Annaba, Algeria

in linkedin.com/in/bouakkadiabrahim

github.com/kiakahaDZ

### **OBJECTIF**

More than 8 years of experience in implementing website design projects, including assembling user requests, producing code, creating patterns and improving designs to impress customers. Focus on creating a robust, impeccable code with exceptional security. Ability to compatibility objectives while satisfying and exceeding customer demands.

#### **COMPETENCE**

- PHP
- Symfony Sylius
- Laravel
- HTML5 CSS Bootstrap
- Angular React JavaScript -TypeScript
- GitHub GitLab
- Basecamp Jira
- MySQL MongoDB SqlServer
- Heroku Windows Linux

- Amazon Products
- Adobe Photoshop- Adobe Illustrator Adobe XD •
- RESTFUL API Express.is
- WordPress

French

- Digitalocean Firebase Laravel forge
- Responsibility
- Agile Development Methods (Clean Architect)
- Front-end Frameworks
- Back-end Architecture

- Teamwork
- Organization
- A sense of communication
- Leadership
- Adaptation
- Customer Relationship
- Autonomy

English

#### LANGUAGE

Arabic

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

August. 2022 – Now

**Computer Engineer** 

Annaba, Algeria

Cnep Bank

- Write the code necessary for the operation of applications
- Test the proper functioning of the site from all points of view (testing) Fix the errors that appeared (debugging)
- Put web applications developed online within established times Develop technical support documentation
- Solve technical problems related to the operation of web applications

July. 2023 – Now Montpellier, France **Full Stack Developer - Freelance** 

Winnr SAS

- Write the code needed to run applications
- Test the proper functioning of the site from all points of view (testing)
  Fix the errors that appeared (debugging)
- Put web applications developed online within established times
  Development of supporting technical documentation
- Solve technical problems related to the operation of web applications
  Stack: AngularJS, Nodejs, Flrebase

**Full Stack Developer** 

+213775225061

bbouakkadia@live.fr
 bouakkadia@live.fr
 bouakkadia@l

Annaba, Algeria

in linkedin.com/in/bouakkadiabrahim

github.com/kiakahaDZ

#### March. 2021 – August. 2022 Full Stack Developer - Freelance

Riyadh, Arabie Saoudite

Tech-station

- Develop web solutions, api, plugins and also development under the e-commerce platforms sylius, prestashop, woocommerce, from the initial concept to the final configuration, according to the specifications of the company such as
- qasralawani.com noragardens.com aleef.com- oudak.sa rpcorp.indio.guru riadiat.sa - www.musicstation.sa - qaser.tech-station.co
- Plugins:
- Payfort Payment Sylius.
- Payfort Call Pay Sylius.
- Tamara Payment Sylius.
- Hyper Pay mada, visa/master, Call Pay. Shop Api.
- Chargily E-Payment Sylius.
- Chargily E-Payment Symphony.
- Mautic cron job plugin.
- Mautic Recommend Bundle migration from symfony 3 to Symfony 4 & 5.
- Write the code necessary for the operation of the site
- Test the proper functioning of the site from all points of view (testing) Fix the errors that appeared (debugging)
- Put the developed website online within the established time, Development of supporting technical documentation
- Solve technical problems related to the operation of the website/web application

march. 2015 - march. 2021

**Full Stack Developer - Freelance** 

Annaba, Algeria

Public establishment Hosptalier

- Work as Assistant Project Manager for the implementation of projects such as Electronic Medical Records Platform for the management of hospitals and care centres.
- Pharmacy Management Platform.
- ERP for Hospital Management Triple Hospital Accounting.

January. 2020 – January. 2021

**Computer Teacher** 

Annaba, Algeria

Le rayon académie

- Teached students by groups:
- Informatics Bureau Group (INTERMEDIAIRE).
- Web Development Group (Initiation).

**Full Stack Developer** 

Annaba, Algeria

inkedin.com/in/bouakkadiabrahim

github.com/kiakahaDZ

June. 2015 – July. 2020

#### **Full Stack Developer - Freelance**

Annaba, Algeria Clinique El-Djazair

- Information system process driver for obtaining ISO9001 quality management system certification.
- Customized web platform according to the need of the clinic GMAO (Computer Assisted Maintenance Management), Pharmacy management, Recreated the logo of the clinic with illustrator, Design of the clinic's website.

June. 2015 – June. 2016

#### **Computer Teacher**

Annaba, Algeria

National Institute of Paramedics

- Teacher Computer Science and Internet Module: Computer Science Module and Internet, The discovery of Windows, Configuration Panel.
- Text Processing Word: write a document, Excel table: design a table, PowerPoint: know how to present documents, Computer security, Search on the Internet (les moteurs de recherche).
- OFFICE (INTERMEDIAIRE)

August. 2012 – avr. 2014

#### **Helpdesk Technician**

Annaba, Algeria

Algerie poste & telecommunications

 Database Administrator, Capturing change requests, Software licensing management, Management of data access, Assistance in problem management, Monitoring of infrastructure and services.

march. 2012 – July. 2012

#### **Helpdesk Technician**

Annaba, Algeria

SARL EAPI EL COQ

- Experience in computer hardware maintenance, network equipment maintenance, develop under the Scrabble software according to the needs of the company and master software such as, GMAO, GPAO.
- Tags: It help desk, System administrator, Database administrator.

ianv. 2012 – march. 2012

**Helpdesk Technician** 

Annaba, Algerie

SARL SAT PAP ALIF

- Experience in computer hardware maintenance, network equipment maintenance, develop under the Scrabble software according to the needs of the company and master software such as, GMAO, GPAO.
- Tags: It help desk, System administrator, Database administrator.

**Full Stack Developer** 

+213775225061

Annaba, Algeria

linkedin.com/in/bouakkadiabrahim github.com/kiakahaDZ

mai. 2011 – June. 2011

**Technical internship** 

Annaba, Algeria

ALGERIE TELECOM SPA

Internship End of study Academic degree

#### **TRAINING**

Master of Science in Computer Science Software Engineering (Master's Degree

2009 - 2014 Annaba, Algeria

**Equivalent)** 

badji mokhtar annaba University

2008

**Bachelor of Science (Equivalent Bachelor's Degree)** 

Annaba, Algeria

EL-BOUNI 1 High School

### Certificates, training

Online Court Certificate (Udemy) React Fundamentals - Udemy

Create a CRM with React.js - LinkedIn Learning

Node.js and Express: Building APIs - LinkedIn Learning

### **CENTRES D'INTÉRÊT**

- Cinema
- Association Activities
- Music
- Reading